Abhishek P

UX Designer

I am a UX designer who wants to create intuitive and meaningful experiences for the user, across industries and demographies. With over 3 years of experience as a developer, I look forward to bringing over my expertise across both the fields and help you build your product.

Contact

Social



abhisheknr4@gmail.com



+91 9986551570

&

@abhisheknairofficial



github.com/abhisheknairofficial

https://www.abhisheknairofficial.com

In

@abhisheknairofficial linkedin.com/in/6foot4

medium.com/@abhisheknairp

Experience

Product Engineer | PiktorLabs

June 2019 - Present

- Led the front end team effort for a product.
- Integrated analytics and performance metrics into the product using firebase.
- Reduced application size by 60% and improved overall performance.
- Part of the team responsible for recruitment and training.

Software Engineer | Moonraft Innovation Labs

Sept 2017 - May 2019

- Led the Front-end development team.
- Worked closely with the design and API teams.
- Was the main point of contact for client.
- Part of the team responsible for recruitment and training.

Education

UX/UI course | Designboat School

July 2020 - Nov 2020

B.E. Mechanical Engineering | UVCE

Aug 2013 - June 2017

Skills

Research

Stakeholder analysis, Design Strategy, Interviews, persona creation, surveys, user journey mapping.

Design

Information architecture, wireframing, visual design, interactive prototypes, Material UI, micro interactions.

Tools & Technical

Adobe XD, Sketch, Invision Studio.

HTML, CSS, JS, in-depth knowledge of the development side.

Certifications

User Experience Design Essentials | Udemy

June 2020

Achievements

Enterprise Design thinking | IBM

Aug 2020

Daily UI Challenge | Daily UI

Feb 2020 - June 2020